This is pretty much what's happened so far.
到目前为止大概是这样子…
Ross was in love with Rachel since forever.
打从一开始罗斯就爱瑞秋
Every time he tried to tell her, something got in the way...
但每次他想要表白 总是会遇上阻碍…
...Iike cats,Italian guys.
像是猫咪，意大利佬
And finally,Chandler was, like,"Forget about her."
最后钱德劝他死心
When Ross was in China,Chandler let it slip that Ross loved Rachel.
罗斯去中国考古时 钱德说漏嘴罗斯爱瑞秋
She was,like,"Oh,my God!"
瑞秋非常惊讶
So she went to the airport to meet him.
于是她到机场接罗斯
She didn 't know Ross was getting off the plane with another woman.
她不知道罗斯 带了另一个女人下飞机
That's pretty much everything you need to know.
大概就是这样子了
But enough about us. How have you been?
说够了我们，你们近来如何？
The One With Ross' New Girlfriend
-=BT之家DRM小组 http://bbs.btbbt.com=- 河马压缩制作 本字幕为河马根据R3DVD OCR得来
六人行 第2季 第01集 罗斯的新女友
Flight number 457 from Beijing now arriving.
从北京飞来第457号班机 已经降落
Oh,my God!
我的天啊！
天啊！
Excuse me.
对不起
Move,move,move! Emergency,please!
借过，借过！ 紧急事件，拜托！
Excuse me,excuse me.
对不起，对不起
There you are!
原来你们在那里！
So,so....
所以，所以…
How was China? You!
中国怎么样？老兄！
It was great.
很棒…
What happened?
你怎么啦？
-You're bleeding. -I am?
你在流血 是吗？
Oh,look at that! Yes,I am.
啊，怪怪！我是在流血
Enough about me, Mr. Back From The Orient!
别管我了 周游东方的旅人！
Come on,I wanna hear everything! Everything!
我要听一切事情！ 什么都不要漏掉！
Well,where do I start?
嗯，要从何开始？
This is Julie. Julie,this is Rachel.
这位是茱莉 茱莉，这位是瑞秋
These are....
这些…
These are...
...aren't for you.
…不是要给你的
These are for you.
这些是要送给你的
Welcome to our country.
欢迎光临敝国
Thank you. I'm from New York.
谢谢，我是纽约人
No problem. We'll use them to stop the bleeding.
没关系，我用它来止血
Baggage claim?
去拿行李？
She went to the airport,and she's gonna go for it with Ross.
她去了机场 准备跟罗斯坦白了
Oh,my God! This is huge!
天啊！这是大事！
This is bigger than huge. This is....
这比大事还大 这是…
All right,what's bigger than huge?
什么比大事还大？
This?
这件事吗？
Guys,you got new haircuts!
喂，你们剪头发了！
Yes,we did. Thanks to Vidal Buffay.
是的，谢谢布菲美发大师
Because,you know,"lf you don't look good,we don't look good."
因为如果你们丢脸 我们也丢脸（广告词）
I love that voice!
我喜欢这声音！
You guys!
各位！
Airport. Airport. Ross.
机场…机场…罗斯
Not alone.
不是一个人
Julie.
茱莉
Arm around her!
搂着她！
Cramp! Cramp! Cramp!
抽筋！抽筋！
I think she's trying to tell us something.
她好像想说什么
Quick,get the verbs.
赶快猜动词
You! You!
你！你！
You said he liked me!
你说他喜欢我！
You!
你！
You slowpokes!
你这个慢O中！
That's all right. We got the bags.
没关系，我们拿了行李
This is my sister,Monica.
这是我妹妹摩妮卡
This is Chandler.
这是钱德
Phoebe,hi.
菲比，嗨
Joey.
乔伊
Everyone,this is Julie.
各位，这位是茱莉
Julie.
茱莉
But I'm not here, you haven't met me.
但我还没到 我们还没见面
I'll make a better impression when I don't have 20 hours of plane on me.
没有连坐二十小时飞机 明天我会让各位刮目相看
-And bus. -Oh,my God!
还有巴士 喔，天啊！
-With the screaming guy -And the spitting.
那个尖叫的砘铩 还有吐口水
You gotta hear this story.
你们一定要听这个故事
We're on this bus that's 200 years old.
我们坐的巴士一定有两百年旧
Two hundred,at least.
至少两百年旧
And the chicken poops in her lap!
一只鸡拉屎在她腿上！
I'm so sorry.
对不起
I just gave away the ending,didn't l?
我说出了结尾，对不对？
I just heard this story in the cab...
我在计程车上听了这个故事…
...and it is all I can think about.
…满脑子想的都是这个
This is amazing.
真是惊人
How did this happen?
怎么发生的？
We were in grad school together.
罗斯与我一起上过研究所
We haven't seen each other since then. I land in China...
后来就没有再见面 我降落在中国机场时…
...guess who's in charge of the dig?
…猜猜是谁负责探勘？
Julie!
就是茱莉！
Isn't that great?
真是太棒了！
Isn't that just kick-you-in-the-crotch, spit-on-your-neck fantastic?
真是棒得面红耳赤！ 棒得有苦说不出！
It's an expression.
她习惯这么说
We just wanted to say a quick hi.
我们只是来打个招呼
-Then we'll see the baby. -Then get some sleep.
然后我们要去看宝宝 然后睡一下觉
It's 6:00 tomorrow night,our time.
现在是中国的明天晚上六点
Don't tell us what's gonna happen. I like being surprised.
别告诉我会发生什么事 我比较喜欢惊喜
Bye!
再见！
中央公园咖啡店
-Can I get some coffee? -Sure.
瑞秋，我想喝点咖啡 没问题
-Did you talk to him yet? -No.
你跟他谈了吗？ 没有
Then,no.
没咖啡给你
What the hell happened to you in China?
你在中国发生了什么事？
When last we left you, you were in love with,you know.
你离开前还疯狂爱着… 你知道的
I know I was.
我知道我爱她
But there was always this voice inside that kept saying:
但我心中有这个小声音告诉我
"It's never gonna happen. Move on." You know whose voice that was?
不可能成功的，死心吧 你知道那是谁的声音吗？
God?
上帝？
It was you,pal.
是你的声音，老哥
Maybe it was God doing me.
也许是上帝模仿我的声音
You were right. She looks at me and sees a friend. That's all.
你说得对 她眼中只把我当成朋友
And then I met Julie...
然后我遇见了茱莉
...and we're having a great time.
我们在一起非常开心
I never would have gone for it, if it hadn't been for you.
要不是因为你 我绝不会跟茱莉在一起
Well,you owe me one,big guy.
你欠我一个情，大个儿
Your lemonade.
你的柠檬汁
I didn't order it.
我没有叫柠檬汁
Then go take that back. They'll charge you for that.
那你最好送回去 否则他们会要你付钱！
Go,go,go! Come on,come on!
快！快！快去！
So what did you find out?
你问出了什么？
He said....
他说…
They're having a great time.
他们在一起很开心
I'm sorry.
对不起
But the silver lining, if you wanna see it...
但有好的一面 如果你愿意这么看…
...is that he made this decision all by himself...
他完全是自己做了这个决定
...without any outside help whatsoever.
完全没有受外人的影响
How is that a silver lining?
这怎么是好的一面？
You have to really wanna see it.
你要非常愿意才看得出来
Ironically,these guys were picked last in gym.
讽刺的是这些砘 上体育课时没人愿意跟他一队
Hey,Pheebs.
菲比
You know what I'm thinking?
你知道我想什么吗？
How...
因为…
...it's been so long since you've had sex...
你太久没做爱了…
...you're wondering if they've changed it?
你不知道有没有什么改变？
No. Although now that's what I'm thinking.
不是 但是我现在是这么想了
So what were you thinking?
你本来在想什么？
You gave the guys great haircuts. I thought you'd like to do mine.
你帮他们剪头发 我想你也应该帮我剪
No.
不要
Why not?
为什么不要？
Because I'm just....
因为我是个…
I'm incredibly anal and an unbelievable control freak.
我非常挑剔 而且有控制狂
No,you're not.
不，你才不是
I know I'm not,but you are.
我知道我不是 不过你是
I was trying to spare your feelings.
我只是不想伤害你的心
Hold on.
请等一下
Ross,Julie for you.
罗斯，茱莉找你
Anybody know a good tailor?
谁能介绍一个好裁缝？
You need clothes altered?
需要改衣服吗？
No,I'm just looking for a man to draw on me with chalk.
不，我只是要找一个人 用粉笔在我身上画线
Go see Frankie. My family's been going to him forever.
去找法兰基 我家人都找他做衣服
He did my first suit when I was 1 5.
我十五岁第一套西装 就是他做的
No,wait,1 6.
不，十六岁
No,excuse me,1 5.
不，对不起，是十五岁
All right,when was 1 990?
1990年是几岁？
You have to stop the Q-Tip when there's resistance!
当你掏耳朵时 碰到东西就要停下来！
Sweetheart,I'll see you later.
甜心，待会见
Okay,bye.
好，再见
That is so sweet.
你真好
Okay. No,you hang up.
好，不，你先挂
No,you
不，你先…
One,two,three.
一，二，三
You didn't hang up either.
你也没有挂
She didn't hang up.
她没挂
No,you hang up.
不，你挂电话
You. You.
你挂，你挂
Sorry,I thought you were talking to me.
对不起，我以为你在跟我说话
Rachel.
瑞秋！
I'll just call her back.
我打回去
Hi,sweetie. I'm sorry. We got disconnected.
嗨，甜心，对不起 我们被中断了
No,you hang up.
不，你挂掉
How did this happen to me?
我到底是怎么回事？
A week ago,two weeks ago,I was fine.
一周前，两周前，我很好
Ross was just Ross. Just this guy.
罗斯只是罗斯 这是这个砘
Now all of a sudden,he's Ross...
现在突然间，他不一样了
...this really great guy that I can't have.
变成这个大帅哥 我却无法得到
Sweetie,I wanted you to have him too.
甜心，我也希望你能得到他
I know you did.
我知道你的心意
I'm just gonna deal with it.
我必须要想办法
I gotta get out of here!
我必须要离开这里！
I don't care what you guys say, something's bothering her.
我不管你们怎么说 她有心事
You know,I think I was 1 6.
我想我是十六岁
Please,just a little bit off the back.
求求你，只要剪后面一点点
I'm still on "no."
我还是坚持不要
Morning.
早安
Could you close your eyes for a sec?
你们能不能闭上眼睛一秒钟？
No,no,no. I'm not falling for that again.
不，不，不 我可不要再上当
What's going on?
怎么回事？
I sort of did a stupid thing last night.
昨晚我做了一件蠢事
What stupid thing did you do?
你做了什么蠢事？
Why don't you just go get dressed...
你为什么不穿上衣服…
...then you'll be on your way. Bye-bye.
然后就可以走了，再见
How did this happen?
怎么发生的？
I kind of ran into him last night.
我昨晚凑巧碰到他
-Where? -At his apartment.
在哪里碰到他？ 在他的公寓
Is this juice?
这是果汁吗？
And the fact that you dumped him because he hit on Phoebe?
你忘了他勾引菲比 所以你才甩了他？
Oh,God,I know. I'm pathetic,I'm a loser.
天啊，我真是可悲 我是个烂货！
Honey,you're not pathetic. You're just sad.
甜心，你不可悲 你只是伤心
People do stupid things when they're upset.
大家伤心时都会干蠢事
My God,if I had a nickel for every guy I wish I hadn't
如果每个我不该上床的人 都给我五毛钱…
But this is about your horrible mistake.
但这是关于你的大错误
Sorry we're late.
对不起，我们迟到了
We were....
我们…
Well,there was touching.
发生过接触
Hey,Ross!
嗨，罗斯
What a....
真是…
What are you doing here?
你在这里干什么？
I do Raquel!
跟瑞秋嘿咻！
So he's back?
他回来了？
Yeah,he's back. Is that a problem?
对，他回来了 有什么问题吗？
No,not a problem.
没问题
Good. Glad it's not a problem.
很好，没有问题
You're gonna have to not touch my ass.
你不能再碰我的屁股！
Despite the yummy bagels and palpable tension...
尽管有美味的面包 与浓厚的紧张气氛…
... my pants need to be altered.
我要去改裤子了
When you see Frankie, tell him Joey Tribbiani says hello.
你见到法兰基时 替我问个好
He'll know what it means.
他会明白我的意思
You sure he'll crack that code?
你确定他能解得开密码吗？
It's funny. The last time Paolo was here,my hair was so much cuter.
上次波洛来这里时 我的短发要可爱多了
All right.
好吧
But you have to promise that you will not be all controlly and bossy...
但你要保证不会挑剔与专横…
...and all Monica about it.
不会像个摩妮卡
I promise.
我保证
All right,let's see.
好，让我看看
Now,some of you are gonna get cut and some of you aren't.
你们有一些会被剪掉 有些不会
But I promise,none of you will feel a thing.
但我保证绝对不会痛
-That's it. I quit. -What? I didn't say anything!
我不干了 我什么都没说！
But this isn't the face of a person who trusts a person.
但这不是一张信任的表情
This is the face of a person who,you know...
这是一张，你知道的…
...doesn't trust a person.
不信任人的表情
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
对不起，对不起
It's just a little shorter than what we had discussed.
这比我们说的要短了一点
Would you relax? I know what I am doing.
你放轻松好吗？ 我知道要怎么剪
This is how he wears it.
他的发型就是这样
How who wears it?
谁的发型就是这样？
Demi Moore.
黛咪摩儿
Demi Moore is not a "he."
黛咪摩儿不是一个“他”
Well,he was a "he" in Arthur and in 10.
他在“二八佳人花公子” 与“十全十美”都是一个“他”
That's Dudley Moore!
那是杜德利摩尔！
I said I wanted it like Demi Moore!
我说我要像黛咪摩儿！
Oh,my God!
喔，老天！
Oh,God!
天啊！
Oh,my God! I'm sorry!
我的天，真对不起！
Which one is Demi Moore?
黛咪摩儿是哪一个？
She's the actress that was in Disclosure,Indecent Proposal,Ghost!
她是女星！演过桃色机密 桃色交易与第六感生死恋
She's got gorgeous hair.
她的头发非常美！
I know!
我知道！
How long do you want the cuffs?
你的袖子要多长？
At least as long as I have the pants.
至少要跟裤子一样长久
I just got that.
我听懂了
Now we'll do your inseam.
现在要量内缝
How is she?
她的情况如何？
It's too soon to tell.
现在还不知道
She's resting,which is a good sign.
她在休息，这是好徵兆
How's the hair?
头发怎么样？
I'm not gonna lie to you. It doesn't look good.
我不骗你 真的很不好看
I put a clip on one side,which seems to have stopped the curling.
我在一边加上发夹 似乎能阻止卷曲
Can we see her?
我能不能看看她？
Your hair looks too good. It'd upset her.
你的头发太好看了 会让她伤心
Ross,you come on in.
罗斯，你去看看她好了
Well,how you doing?
你还好吗？
I'm okay.
我很好
That bad,huh?
这么糟糕？
Look,I can sense when women are depressed and vulnerable.
我可以感觉到 女人难过脆弱的时候
It's one of my gifts.
这是我的天赋之一
Joey,when I saw him get off that plane with her...
乔伊，当我看到他 与她一起下飞机…
...I really thought I just hit rock bottom.
我以为我坠入了谷底
But today,it's like there's rock bottom...
但今天是谷底…
... 50 feet of crap...
下面还有五十尺厚的垃圾…
...then me.
…然后就是我
Tell Ross how you feel.
你必须告诉罗斯你的感受
Come on,how can I just tell him? What about Julie?
我怎么能告诉他？ 茱莉呢？
What about her? They've only been going out for two weeks.
又怎么样？ 他们才在一起两周
Ross has been in love with you for 10 years.
罗斯已经爱你十年了
I don't know. I don't know.
我不知道，我不知道…
I've been with my share of women.
我交往过很多女人
I've been with a lot of people's share of women.
我交往过很多别人的女人
But the point is...
但重点是…
... I've never felt about anyone the way Ross felt about you.
我从来没有对任何人 像罗斯对你这样专情…
Really?
真的吗？
Yo,paisan!
喂，老兄！
Can I talk to you for a sec?
我能跟你谈一下吗？
Your tailor...
你的裁缝…
...is a very bad man!
是个大坏蛋！
What are you talking about?
你在说什么？
Hey,what's going on?
怎么样？
Joey's tailor...
乔伊的裁缝…
...took advantage of me.
吃了我的豆腐
No way! I've been going to the guy for 1 2 years.
不可能！我去他那里十二年了
He said he was gonna do my inseam.
他说要量我的内缝
Then he ran his hand up my leg and then there was definite
他的手沿着我的腿往上摸 然后就…
What?
什么？
Cupping.
包住了
That's how they do pants!
他们就是这样量裤子的！
First they go up one side, they move it over.
首先量一边 把小弟弟推到一旁
Then they go up the other side, move it back,then they do the rear.
然后量另一边 把小弟弟推回来，然后量后面
Ross,tell him. Isn't that how a tailor measures pants?
罗斯，告诉他 裁缝量裤子不都是这样？
Yes,yes,it is. In prison!
是的，的确是这样 在监狱里！
What's the matter with you?
你是怎么搞的？
What?
什么？
That's not?
不是这样？
Oh,my God!
我的老天！
Even Mary Tyler Moore would've been better.
就算是玛丽泰勒摩尔 也比这个要好
I like it.
我喜欢
I do. I think it's a 10!
真的，我觉得“十全十美”！
Thank you.
谢谢
My hair is very amused.
我的头发很让人开怀
Come on,things could be worse.
事情还可能更糟
You could "get caught between the moon and New York City.
你可能会被“困在纽约月光中” （电影主题曲）
I know it's crazy,but it's true."
我知道很疯狂，不过千真万确 （电影主题曲）
Thank you.
谢谢
Well,I gotta go. Bye.
我要走了，待会见
Bye,Rach!
瑞秋，再见！
Wait,are you leaving?
慢着，你要走了？
That's what I meant by "bye."
所以我才说再见
Can I talk to you for a sec?
我能不能跟你说一下话？
When the doctor does that hernia test....
当医生检查疝气时…
That's okay.
那样做就没有关系
What's going on?
怎么啦？
Well,okay,first of all...
首先…
... Paolo and I are not back together.
波洛与我没有在一起
That was a stupid thing I did.
那是我干的一件蠢事
If I could go back in time and do it again...
如果我能使时光倒转…
...well,I wouldn't.
我绝对不会这么做
Second of all....
其次…
What?
什么？
Is this one of those things where you break up with a guy...
我要先问清楚 这是不是当你与男友分手…
... I tell you what I think...
我告诉你我的想法…
...and the next day you get back together with him...
然后第二天你又重修旧好…
...and I look like a complete idiot?
我变成一个大蠢蛋？
Well,then,I think the guy's scum.
好，我觉得他实在很烂
I hate him. I mean,I actually I physically hate him.
我恨死他了 我真的很厌恶他
I always have.
我一直很厌恶他
And you are way too good to be with a guy like that.
你值得更好的男人
Really?
真的？
You deserve to be with someone who appreciates you...
你值得一个真正能欣赏你的人
...and who gets how funny...
了解你有多么幽默…
...and sweet and amazing...
多么温柔，多么体帖…
...and adorable and sexy you are.
多么美丽性感…
You know? Someone who wakes up every morning thinking:
每天早上醒来都会想着…
"Oh,my God. I'm with Rachel!"
天啊，我跟瑞秋在一起！
You know? Someone who makes you feel good.
这个人能让你感觉非常好
Like the way I do with Julie.
就像我与茱莉一样
Was there a "second of all"?
你还没说完？
No,I think that was the whole "all."
不，我想这就是了
I gotta go.
我要走了
Thanks.
谢谢
No,I swear to God,Dad!
不，我向天发誓，爸！
That's not how they measure pants!
不是这样子量裤子的！
I was thinking of doing it shorter, like Andie MacDowell's haircut.
我想要剪个短发 就像安蒂麦道威尔的发型
-Yeah,I could do that. -Really?
这我会剪 真的？
-You wanna do it now? -Great!
你要现在就剪吗？ 太好了！
See you.
待会见
I just wanna make really sure this time.
这次我要弄清楚
Andie MacDowell is the girl from Four Weddings and a Funeral,right?
安蒂麦道威尔就是演 “你是我今生的新娘”？
No.
不是
That's Roddy McDowall.
那是鲁迪麦道威尔
Andie MacDowell is the guy from Planet of the Apes.
安蒂麦道威尔是演 “浩劫余生”的那个砘
-Thank you. -You're welcome.
谢谢 别客气